

Game Producer / Project Manager

acjh13.github.io

in/acjh13

acjh13@gmail.com

+65 8328 3693

Highly adaptive and multi-disciplinary Producer / Project Manager with a technical and design background. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

Industry Experience

Junior Producer | Lionfish Studios Pte Ltd - Various Projects

Mar 2021 - Present

- Manage communications between development team and project stakeholders
- Manage overall studio resources
- Assist in overseeing project milestones and releases
- Coordinate project development with multiple cross-functional teams

Production Intern | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - Final Fantasy Brave Exvius Sept 2020 - Feb 2021

- Maintained event lists for content updates with Google Sheets and Confluence
- Responsible for Design team's Sprint Planning and follow up with Jira
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Took initiative to streamline and automate various production workflows

On-Campus Experience

Teaching Assistant | DigiPen Singapore – Game Production Class Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

Advised ~10 student teams on project management and game production

Academic Game Projects

Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer

Kindred | Sept 2019 – June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Communicated game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted Agile methodology with weekly Scrum meetings and Kanban boards
- Created cross-department workflows for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Worked with lecturers and team members to resolve internal conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!

Education

Bachelor of Science in **Computer Science and Game Design**

DigiPen Institute of Technology, Singapore Sept 2017 - Apr 2021 (Expected)

- Dean's Honour List, Fall '19
- Exchange Student DigiPen Redmond, Summer '19

Skills

Soft Skills

Effective Communication Problem Solving Conflict Resolution Project Ownership Team Management

Management Methods

Agile Scrum Kanban

Management Software

Jira / Trello Confluence Google / Microsoft Suite Slack / Discord HacknPlan

Software & Tools

Git / SVN Microsoft Office Visual Studio Unity Unreal Engine 4 Custom Game Engine(s)

Programming Languages

C / C++ C# Python JavaScript

Spoken Languages

English (Native) Mandarin (Limited)